testing Ai generate subs, please disable if uncomfortable. warning is removed at 0:15
Hi.
Jiwon unnie's
musical
are you guys waiting for it?
Who's going to see it today?
Is everyone
at the venue
waiting and
watching this live stream right now?
I look exhausted right?
Yeah I just got off work and
earlier
the director
the styling team director said I look really pretty today so
she told me to make sure to
leave a photo or something
so I'm trying to leave something
now
But I do look a bit exhausted
It was so hot that as soon as I got back
I turned on the AC
Wow why is the weather so hot today?
It's just too hot
Jiwon unnie must be super nervous right?
She's probably trembling right now
I hope she does well
My hair looks longer? Yeah my hair grows really fast
Why does it grow so fast?
But I want to have long hair now
I'm a bit sick of short hair
I want to wait until
it gets about
this long
1 year
I'll probably have to wait a year
I want to grow it out fast
But I always wanted to do
short hair in the summer someday
so I was glad I got to do it this time
The background is different today
Of course today
I'm in the living room
Didn't I do it here once before?
I was debating whether to do it or not but
the sunset
here
looks pretty
so I thought it would
come out
looking nice
This is the place
I decorated
This
Fromm Live
is really annoying because
you can't turn it horizontally
So I have to keep showing my left side
How is it?
I hate my left side
Turn the phone?
No I can't then
you'll be able to see
where my house is
I can't do that
I give off mature unnie vibes today?
No but today I really
look like an unnie
Totally
an older sister
an unnie
Totally
Today
I really
slept
a lot
Since I had a lot of schedules until yesterday
my schedule was a bit light today so
wow I slept in for the first time in a while and
it was so
great but
my accumulated
fatigue
still hasn't gone away
If I lower my bangs
it looks like this
My recent vibe?
Ah my recent vibe
is just
nothing
I just
don't really have any specific vibe I want to go for
or anything like that these days
I erased it and started over
Right now I'm just bare-faced
It's not that
Today's TMI
Today I
slept a whole lot
I finished
my schedules and came back
I need
some kind of
content
Turn on the TV
If I turn on the TV
Right
I ordered
braised kimchi
Actually usually
when I do festivals
I
ordered
braised kimchi but
I was so hungry today because yesterday
I ate really little and
was so sleepy
I was really hungry but
I was just too sleepy
so I just fell asleep
and I was so hungry this morning
But
I figured I should eat
after my schedule finished
so I debated between eating
kimchi stew and braised kimchi
that I've been craving since yesterday
and lately I've been into kimchi stew but today
adding ramen to it
was a bit much
so
The fromis_9 fan meeting where you can't laugh
We did that and
the members
were posting it a lot
and we were copying it right next to them
so I tried to hold it in
but I ended up
And then
Is there someone behind me?
How does Hayoung
even do that?
I just go
achoo
just achoo
I'm normal
Normal
I am
normal
Me saying I'm normal is so funny right?
It's cute
Hayoung did that today didn't she?
The weather forecast
It was so cute seeing her
try so hard
to speak clearly
It was really cute
I will now give you today's weather forecast
She was doing that
and it was so cute
It was
really cute
Here it is
Hello
fromis_9
member Song Hayoung
Song Hayoung here
With our recent album
we are delivering refreshing energy for this summer
Ah seriously I keep showing it off. Like a vitamin
I hope we can
deliver lively energy to you all
We will continue to
bring you good music
Then from now on
I will deliver
today's weather
Isn't she so cute?
Today in most regions across the country
we will see
sweltering weather
The highest daytime temperatures
Ah I don't think I can do this
If I do it
I'd really be like
38 degrees
The whole country
will range from 32
to 38 degrees
overall
As this sweltering weather continues
heatwave warnings
will also continue
nationwide
In Jeonnam
Gwangyang and
Daegu and central
Gyeongsang
severe heatwave advisories have been issued
Oh
I'm pretty good at this
Pretty good
But you know we can't practice this guys
You know we can't practice it right?
Because
weathercasters
since the weather
keeps
changing like this
they have to do it
live
since it changes constantly
Anyway that's what I heard
that you can't practice because it changes in real time
At the pop-up store
my nose print is still there?
Wow that's too much
They didn't wipe it off?
Ah really?
They really
should have wiped that off
Man
That's a bit
You took a proof shot?
That's too much
That's crossing the line
Ah
that's a bit embarrassing
Do I regret it?
No
I just wanted to look cute
so I pressed my nose against it
but it
came out looking a bit
like a weird memory
I thought getting squished like this
would look really cute
and that's what I expected
when I did it
but it got way more squished than I thought
There aren't cheek prints
too right?
There shouldn't be. But I'm pretty sure I wiped it.
Maybe someone else
Maybe someone else did it guys
Right now I have a lot of
canker sores on my tongue
so my pronunciation is a bit slurred right now
It's really slurred. More than usual.
Again
Yeah I
get them all the time so
they're basically a part of me now
So
I was told it's genetic
Wait a second
Ta-da
I bought this because it was cute but
it's a bit
ugly
I usually wear it like this at home
because my bangs are
too short
to sweep back
like usual
so I just
clip it up like this
Ta-da
I think my left side looks okay today
It looks fine right? My left side
Right now
exactly like this
I shouldn't turn any further. If I turn more I'll look ugly.
Exactly at 45 degrees like this
Looks good right?
Why do I kind of like it right now?
Hold on let me try using a filter here
Ah it's too strong
Wait a minute
Should I
add more makeup on here?
This one is kind of cute right?
It has a bit of that
do you know what vibe this is? The SODA app vibe
Instagram Paris filter vibe
My left side
doesn't look bad today. I like it.
B612?
Ah B612
doesn't have this vibe. B612
is a bit more
yellow
blue and
green
Rather than a soft vibe
it feels more like a heavy filter. This one is more like SNOW.
Shiny forehead
Ah
Flover is here
They're here
Kimchi is delicious right?
Wow
it looks so good
Ah but is it better without the filter?
I feel like
everything
is exposed
right now. Because of the sunlight
my face
right now
Ah
Actually
my skin
has gotten a bit worse
recently so guys
please be careful. This skin is not my real skin.
Even if my skin looks a bit bumpy
it's probably from lack of sleep. Because I haven't been sleeping well.
So my skin
isn't breaking out
but the texture
is really
rough
It feels bad
when I wash my face
It's supposed to be really smooth when I wash it
I'll just have to get help from the filter
Today I'll go with this slightly cold vibe
Eat my food?
I'll go get it first
Should I turn it off and eat?
Showing myself eating is a bit
doing a mukbang isn't really
my thing
Alright
Tell me when Jiwon unnie's musical starts guys.
Because I'm going to turn this off.
It starts in 30 minutes? What time is it now? Is it 7?
It starts at 8 right?
I'm not sure when it starts since it's a grand theater
I don't know much about grand theaters
There's so much tofu
Wow
Am I on a diet?
That must be hard
It's hard to watch right?
Mm
Ta-da
Ah
It's so good
Cola is dangerous
Why?
Okay then I should be careful
and not
drink it
We're in our 9th year?
But
do you know
how many years our team
thinks we've been around for?
We live thinking we're in our 3rd or 4th year
Our team
still has a lot we haven't tried so even though it's our 9th year
we somehow
what should I say?
Don't have that 9th-year
vibe
Even though it's our 9th year
we only have the experience level of a
4th or 5th year group
So
the members always
tell each other
let's live thinking we're in our 4th or 5th year
Because it's only been
about 2 or 3 years since
many people started to recognize us
So we
live
like that
So
when people around us
see our members
doing live streams
and stuff
they get really
surprised
Especially Hayoung she turns it on
really often
Live streams too
and people
get surprised
But due to our members' nature
I wanted to go see Jiwon today
but Jiwon
said today wouldn't work
so I thought about just going to hang out
but it wasn't a good idea
I'll go together with the members
next time
It's great
That venue
shouldn't be bad. Actually
I'm not sure if it's the place I've been to before
Am I only eating tofu? Tofu is my favorite
When eating braised kimchi or stew
the tofu and
mushrooms
are so delicious
I do have rice
Ah I'm full
My stomach has gotten a bit smaller now
Cool right?
I dieted really hard
and then I'll wait
about a minute
and start eating again
Don't worry
It's not here
I thought there was seaweed but there isn't
Alright
Starting again
The fullness has
gone away a bit
Saying I'm full
for the first time
is just a sign that
it's just beginning
It's kind of like a
habitual phrase
right?
Habitual
The tofu is so good
What do I do? I added four extra portions of tofu to this
Kia
won?
That's because they didn't invite me
They won every time I went
but they didn't invite me
It's because they didn't invite me this time
I'm not sulking
I'm just a little upset
Yeah
Recently my mom asked me to go to a baseball game with her but I was preparing for promotions
How can I go to a baseball game during promotions?
Alright the 2nd wave of fullness is here
2nd wave of fullness
I don't know how many waves of fullness there will be
I want Yoajung
Wow
Flover
I want to eat Yoajung
Wait
I weighed myself
this morning and
I actually
lost a lot of weight
I usually gain weight during promotions
but during these promotions
all the members didn't really eat much
We focused more
on sleeping so
since the members weren't eating
I ended up not eating either
So
yeah
When we did Miniskirt I was
48kg
Anyway I think it was around there
But now I've
lost about 3kg
I fluctuate between 44 and 45kg
But I don't look like it right?
Ah I'm full
Ah I'm so full
Wow
Uh
So full
But guys probably
don't know how skinny
45kg is
Right now
I'm just bones
Ah I guess not that much. These days
idols are so
skinny
But
by my standards
by my own personal standards
I really
cannot lose any more weight from here
I don't want to lose any more weight and
if I lose more
ah
life would be too
hard and upsetting
my whole life
But everyone saying I look pretty lately is all
probably because I lost a lot of weight
So
I'm planning to maintain this weight
The reason I'm eating now is um
because I
lost some weight today
so I'm eating
to maintain it
Mm
Ah
The 3rd wave of fullness
is here
The 3rd wave is here
Wow you're the same height as me
but we have a 20kg difference?
What?
That's not
fat at all
That's fine
It's just that I'm
an idol
Because of the nature of our job
you guys
have to keep that in mind
Our younger friends
you should never
starve yourselves. Eat lots of delicious food.
I also
eat a lot of delicious food during our off-season
See? When we did Miniskirt I did that too. Yeah.
And also
when was it?
During that era
I was also a bit
heavier than my usual
promotion weight
and couldn't maintain it
I was 46
or 47
I don't really remember. I could be completely wrong but
anyway
Back then
I was a bit chubby
Guys the reason I
always said I'd diet but only did it properly this time is because
before I hit my mid-20s
I wanted to look good in
whatever clothes I wore
I wanted to look really slender and delicate
Next year at the pretty age of 25
you want me to dance to it?
I'll think about it
I'll probably dance to it
someday won't I?
Ah
But you know what? Even when I'm full
if there's food in front of me
I just keep eating it
Especially Korean food. With Korean food
does it just keep going in?
Ah
I really want to eat Yoajung
Ah I want to eat Yoajung
I want
Yoajung
Ah
Or Sulbing
I want to eat something
sweet right now
You want something sweet too right?
Bingsu
or Yoajung
What should I eat?
Or Yogurt World
Bingsu
I don't have Polapo at home right now
I actually do have some leftover
but eating leftovers is a bit sad
Ah I do have Polapo. But that's a bit sad.
Alright then I'll be right back
I'll be
right back. Bye.